[{"question": "  hey...", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " pheebs, what's wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " oh, i'm just so exhausted from dragging around this...  huge engagement ring!", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " my god!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " congratulations! wow!!", "answer": " so, did he get on one knee, did he have a speech prepared, or  did he cry?  yeah, big surprise, i like proposals!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " well, it was really sweet, and like the most romantic thing ever.", "answer": " well, hey! well...  here's to phoebe, who's found the greatest guy in the world! to phoebe and...  i wanna say mike?  to phoebe and mike!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " whoo!", "answer": " thank you!  oh, and i have something for you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " mmh-mmh!", "answer": " it's, yes, my little black book. it's got the numbers of all the guys i've dated.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " oh, pheebs, baby, that's nice but, you know what, i think i'm ok. why don't you give it to one of your other single girlfriends?", "answer": " i would, but you're the last one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": "  give me the book!  pablo diaz, brady smith, huh, &quot;guy-in-van&quot;?", "answer": " oh, my first love!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " what does the red x next to bob greenmore's name mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " dead.  oh, it's ok, no, he was old, yeah! and he lived a full life, he was in the first wave at omaha beach.", "answer": " hey, i'm sorry, i should have given you guys my black book when i got married! although it wasn't so much a book as a... napkin. with janice's phone number on it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " phoebe, isn't jethro tull a band?", "answer": "  oh yes, they are. opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  hey honey!", "answer": "  hi sweetie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " is monica not here?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " oh, then i'll tell you. my agency was bidding for a big account and they got it! it's my first national commercial!", "answer": " cool!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " yeah, and i don't wanna brag but a lot of the ideas were mine!  hell, you weren't there? all the ideas were mine!!!", "answer": " that's great! hey, can you cast me in it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " oh... i don't know, i really don't think you're right for the part.", "answer": " what do you mean? i can do anything, i'm a chameleon! huh?  i'm old!  i'm tired!  hey, i'm hot  i'm cold!! huh?? come on! what can't i do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " first of all. bravo. uh, but i really don't think you're right for this. the part calls for a stuffy college professor.", "answer": " i can do that!  &quot;hello, i'm your professor. when i'm not busy thinking of important things or... professing. i like to use...&quot; oh, what's the product?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " software that facilitates inter-business networking e-solutions?", "answer": "  i'm cold!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " guess who's a finalist for a huge research grant! i'll give you a hint, he's looking right at you.", "answer": " ah, well, unless it's the creepy guy with his hand up his kilt, i'm gonna say congratulations!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh, i'm so excited, i mean, apparently i beat out hundreds of other applicants, included five guys i went to graduate school with. not that i'm keeping score or anything... five!", "answer": " wow, that's great! so, tell me about the grant!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " well, ok, it's for 25 thousand dollars. and if i get it, i'll finally be able to complete my field research! and there will be an article about me in the &quot;paleontology review&quot;! yeah! that'll be the first time my name is in there, without people raising serious questions about my work!", "answer": " wait. are you talking about the dewar grant?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " yeah. why?", "answer": " benjamin hobart is administering that grant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " your ex-boyfriend?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " so, your ex-boyfriend is gonna determine if your new boyfriend gets this grant? wow, your new boyfriend is screwed!", "answer": " no, no, we ended up in great terms. i mean, if anything, i think this could help you. you know what? why don't we all go out to dinner together, and i can introduce you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " well, if you think it would help.", "answer": " yes, absolutely. i'll call him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " ok, now, is there anything i can do to... you know, butter him up? anything he really likes?", "answer": " mmh... he does have a pretty serious latex fetish.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey, you wanna go to see a movie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " well, i told you i had to spend all the day clearing out stuff, so mike could move in.", "answer": " oh, right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " oh, well. now that i'm here i might as well help you with the cleaning and organizing! just happen to have my label maker!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh, it's so hard to get rid of stuff! did you and chandler have to make compromises when you first moved in together?", "answer": " uh, chandler did! what does he want you to give up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " a bunch of stuff. and the worst one... he wants me to get rid of gladys.", "answer": " who's gladys?  oh! what a tragic loss!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " yeah. i really hate to give her up. oh, i know!! oh, you should take her!", "answer": "  well, i-i-i-i... i don't know...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " why, you don't like her?", "answer": " well, of course i do. what's not to like! i'll take her in a minute! but, you know, i think that you're giving up too easy, honey. i think that you need to fight for her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " really? you think?", "answer": " absolutely! yes, you say to him &quot;i'm sorry mike i can't live without her, she means too much to me!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " ok, i'll fight for her. ok! oh, wait, oh i just realized... if i do that, that means you don't get her.", "answer": " damn it, i did not think this through!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hey you guys.", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh! any word on casting yet?", "answer": " joe, i told you, you're just not right for the part.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " what do you mean? rach, don't i seem like a professor you'd buy some kind of e-crap from?", "answer": " i'm sorry, this sounds like something i'm never gonna be interested in. joey : look, c'mon, please? it's not like i'm asking for some crazy favour. this is what i do for a living. i am a professional actor!  oh, man, i'm two hours late for work! . look, here's a copy of my reels. it's got all the commercials that i've been in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " joe...", "answer": " just watch it, and if you don't like it, you don't pass it on to your bosses!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " fine!", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " work, joe!", "answer": " damn it!  chandler : what am i gonna do now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " just pass it to your boss!", "answer": " he's not right for the part. so if i suggest him, my bosses are gonna think i'm an idiot! and that's something they should learn on their own!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " just tell joey that you watched the tape and you liked it, but your bosses didn't. then that way, you're the good guy and they're the bad guys.", "answer": " that's good! i liked it, they didn't.  joey, for god's sake, go to work! .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " i can't believe i'm about to meet benjamin hobart. i've always thought of him as one of the people i'd invite to my fantasy dinner party. do you think there's any chance he'll bring christie brinkley or c3po?", "answer": "  sorry, looks like it's just him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " charlie! my god, you look absolutely stunning!", "answer": " well, i... i am having a good hair day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " so good to see you.", "answer": " me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " i'm ok.", "answer": " i'm sorry...  ross geller... benjamin hobart.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " it's an honor to meet you. i can't tell you how long i've been an admirer of your work, i mean, that nobel prize,  whoooo! i mean, i have to tell you that, you're one of the reasons i got into the field.", "answer": " oh, well, likewise. actually, not likewise. i've never heard of you until this morning, but, it's nice to be nice!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " shall we? .", "answer": "  thank you! . i can't believe that you chose this restaurant! do you remember the night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " oh my god, i completely forgot!  oh my god! i can't believe they let us back in this place! . benjamin : you weren't there!", "answer": " no, but, it's, you know, it's just a funny image, you know, the two of you, in this restaurant, with... tzz-zzz, mmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " ross, why don't you tell benji about your proposal, while i go to the ladies room?", "answer": " so, tell me about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " ok well, i would like to do a dig in the painted desert.", "answer": " m-m.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " see, there are still several areas that haven't been fully excavated.", "answer": " break up with charlie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " did you just say &quot;break up with charlie&quot;?", "answer": " well, yes, and now. yes i did say it, and no, i didn't not say it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " kind of inappropriate, don't you think?", "answer": " i'm sorry. i just haven't seen her for so long! all these feelings are rushing back! i'm starting to realize how much i missed her, and i'm gonna need you to break up with her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " are you serious?", "answer": " if you say yes then i'm serious, if you say no then i'm joking!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " joking it is!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " hi! sorry, i'm late.", "answer": " hey, how did it go with mike, is he gonna let you keep the painting?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " no, he really hates it. but he's gonna let me keep my box of human hair! so you got to pick your battles. but the good news is, gladys is yours!", "answer": " wow, what's the bad news!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " who's gladys?", "answer": " oh, she's that work of art i made, you know, with the woman coming out of the frame.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  oh, and monica gets to keep her? in her house? i am so jealous!", "answer": " oh, i didn't know you wanted her too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " huh!", "answer": " well, i mean, sure, of course. but... you already gave that to monica, so...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " you know, i would give her up, for you.", "answer": " no, i couldn't let you do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " but i want to.", "answer": " but i don't want you to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " but i insist!", "answer": " but i insist harder!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " girls, girls, stop, ok? we'll flip a coin. heads, she's rachel's, tails she's monica's. . tails! monica, she's yours!", "answer": " no, that landed in your food!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " hey joe!", "answer": " what's up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " bad news. i watched the tape and passed it along to my bosses and they weren't interested.", "answer": "  oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": "  i'm sorry man.", "answer": "  but, ehm... you watched the tape?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  yeah! i... i... i liked it!  but, ehm... my bosses didn't go for it. stupid sons of bitches!", "answer": "  you didn't watch the tape.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": "  what!? of course i did!", "answer": " look, it's one thing not to cast me, but to lie to me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " i'm not lying to you, i watched it!", "answer": " well, you lied again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " i watched it!", "answer": " keep going pinocchio!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "   i did!", "answer": "  no you didn't!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " the selection committee has chosen the three of you as our finalists today. the ultimate decision will be based upon the answers you give to the questions i ask here. i'm gonna start with dr. li. dr. li, you claim the field is too reliant on the linnaean taxonomic system. how do you propose to correct this problem?", "answer": " well, i believe that the answers lie in the osteological evidence. i plan to begin there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  interesting.", "answer": "  i guess!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " dr. biely, your proposal includes some field work. where might that take place?", "answer": " primarily in the pierre shale region of south dakota.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " certainly. very well. and dr. geller, when is my birthday?", "answer": "  what? i... i...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " care to venture a guess?", "answer": "  may 12th?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": "  that's not even kinda close!  dr. li, how many graduate students you'd be needing?", "answer": " half a dozen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " i see, and dr. biely?", "answer": " three for excavation and two for analysis.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " certainly. dr. geller, which 1965 shirelles hit was later covered by a popular british invasion band?", "answer": "  wha..? i need 6 graduate students.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " no! i'm sorry, we were looking for &quot;baby it's you&quot;. baby it's you.", "answer": " wha...? wait, wait, wait, just a minute. none of my questions have anything to do with paleontology.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " you're right, i apologize. scratch the last question. spell &quot;boscodictiasaur&quot;.", "answer": "  um... i've never heard of a &quot;boscodictiasaur&quot;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " yeah, i just made it up. spell it.", "answer": "  ok.  b - o - s ...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " no, it starts with a silent &quot;m&quot;.", "answer": " oh come on!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " i can't believe joey. i hate being called a liar!", "answer": " but you are a liar.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " you still here?", "answer": " yes, and i have to say, i am not just hurt. i am insulted. when i tell somebody i did something...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " ok whoah-hey... let me just stop you right there, ok? first, you lied, right? then, you lied about lying, ok? then you lied about lying about lying, ok? so before you lie about lying about lying about lying about... lying...   stop lying!", "answer": " why are you so sure i didn't watch this tape?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  oh, my!", "answer": "  wow!  oh, she's so nice and big! oh, monica, where are you going to display gladys oh so proudly?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": "  i haven't really settled on a spot yet!", "answer": " well, hey! how about right above the tv? . that way, it will be the first thing that you see when you walk in the door!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": "  yeah, yeah! and you can get rid of that french poster.", "answer": "  i like that poster!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " really? it doesn't have anything coming out of it. or maybe there is some place for her in your bedroom?", "answer": "  oh! there's nothing above your bed!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh hi! hello! uh, have you come to ask me some more paleontology related questions? uhm... your grandmother's nickname, perhaps?  aunt margaret's pants size?", "answer": " i've come here to apologize. i think i may have let my feelings for charlie interfere with the interview process.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": "  no! stop!", "answer": " anyway, i've decided to offer you the grant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": "  really?", "answer": " well... there is just one small... stipulation...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " i have to break up with charlie?", "answer": " hey, you got one right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " you're crazy.", "answer": " crazy, or... romantic?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " crazy!", "answer": " ooor...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " o-oh my god!", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " joey, what... is... this...thing... doing here?", "answer": " i got it from monica. she sold it to me for a very reasonable price.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " joey, we're not keeping this!", "answer": " but it's an original buffay...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " alright, fine. you can keep it. as long as you don't mind that she's haunted.", "answer": " hey? what? what? wey! whoo! what? what!?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " she climbs out of the frame, and then drags her half-a-body across the floor, just looking for legs to steal.  and then with her one good hand, she slo-o-owly re-e-a-aches up and turns your doorknob.", "answer": " get that legless witch out of here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " hey! i sold that to joey.", "answer": " well, why i told him it's haunted. two can play at this game.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " no you can't. she's yours!", "answer": " she's yours!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " she's yours!", "answer": " she's yours!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " she's mine!", "answer": " she's m-i-i-ne!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " she's mine!", "answer": " she's mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " i want gladys!", "answer": " she's mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " she's mine!", "answer": " she's mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " look, i'm sorry i didn't give them your tape. and i promise, next time to submit you whether i think you are right for the part or not.", "answer": " that's not the point chandler. the point is that you lied.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " excellent!", "answer": " now, what do you say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " lying is wrong!", "answer": " and?... and?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " i'm a pretty little girl.", "answer": " i knew it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " your ex-boyfriend is insane.", "answer": " did you get the grant?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " no i didn't, and you want to know why? because your ex-boyfriend is still in love with you.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " yeah. he wouldn't give me the grant, because i wouldn't give you up.", "answer": " benji isn't in love with me. i mean, he broke up with me. and besides, he's a very ethical man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " really? is it ethical to ask someone in a grant review, who was the voice of &quot;underdog&quot;?", "answer": " i'm sure he was just joking, ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " if you don't believe me, let's go talk to him, okay? i'm telling you, he didn't ask me one paleontological question.", "answer": " seriously?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " oh, i'm sorry, no. he did ask me one. uhm... how do you spell mboscodictiosaur?", "answer": " well, if it's like the lake mbosco in congo, then m-b-o...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " dr. geller...? charlie... what are you... what are you doing here?", "answer": " i want you to tell her everything. about the deal you tried to make with me, about the crazy questions you... wally cox! that's the voice of underdog!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " like i tried to tell you in the interview ross, this grant is not based on your knowledge of pretty useless trivia.", "answer": " no, no, no. don't do that! i want you to look her in the eyes, and tell her the truth.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " benji?", "answer": " alright, it's true. i behaved horribly. but it's only because i still love you. and i would do anything to have you back in my life.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " too little, too late, benji!", "answer": " i can't believe this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " i never should have broken up with you. i think about you all the time. i mean, do you ever still think about me?", "answer": "  no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " i don't know what to say, benji. this is all so.... romantic.", "answer": " or...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " listen, i know, i may be way out of bounds here, but is there any chance you will take me back?", "answer": " maybe...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " sweetie, this conversation is starting to make me a little uncomfortable.", "answer": " oh god! i am so sorry, but...  i mean it's... there's so much history between us, you know...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " i love you!", "answer": " i love you too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " ha ha ha, third time this week. man, this does not get old.", "answer": " you're mean!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}]